https://www.smcm.edu/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicySt. Mary’s College of Maryland Privacy Statement
Maryland law mandates that State agencies shall not create personal records unless the need for the information is clearly established that personal records are relevant to the purposes for which they are collected, be accurate and current, and will not be obtained by fraudulent means.
State officials who request personal data from citizens must notify the citizens regarding the purposes for which the information is collected, the consequences to the citizen for refusing to provide the personal information, the citizen’s right to inspect and correct personal records, whether the information is generally available for public inspection, and whether the information is made available to other entities.
The State of Maryland is committed to providing you with Web sites over which you may securely and confidently transact business with the State.
Please refer to the eMaryland technology web site for additional information on information technology policies in Maryland»
St. Mary’s College of Maryland reserves the right to provide some or all of the course content through alternative methods of course delivery, including remote methods of delivery, and it reserves the right to change the method of delivery at any time before or during the academic term, in the event of a health or safety emergency or similar situation when it determines, in its sole discretion, that such change is necessary and in the best interests of the College and the campus community.
© 2020 St. Mary's College of Maryland
Consumer Information
Copyright
Privacy Policy
Title IX Compliance &Training
Non-discrimination Policy
Help Desk
Website Feedback
Text HELP to 233733 (BEFREE)
More resources on human trafficking in Maryland
This site uses cookies to provide you with a great user experience. By continuing to use this site, you agree to our cookie policy.
